Society of Southwest Archivists records, Inclusive: 1970-2017, Bulk: 1973-1993, 2003-2016
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- General Membership, 1970-2016, undated; 3
  - Literary: "Committee Policy and Procedure Manual", 1992 February 3 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Literary: "Committee and Procedures Manual", 2001 December (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Literary: "Committee and Procedures Manual", 2003 May (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Literary: "Committee and Procedures Manual" (Notated), circa 2005 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Literary: "Committee and Procedures Manual", 2007 May (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Literary: "Committee and Procedures Manual", 2012 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Literary: Constitution and By-Laws, 1972-1978 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Literary: Constitution, 2005, undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Literary: Draft: Southwest Directory to Archives, Manuscripts, and Historical Records (1 of 4), 1993-1994 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Literary: Draft: Southwest Directory to Archives, Manuscripts, and Historical Records (2 of 4), 1993-1994 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Literary: Draft: Southwest Directory to Archives, Manuscripts, and Historical Records (3 of 4), 1993-1994 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Literary: Draft: Southwest Directory to Archives, Manuscripts, and Historical Records (4 of 4), 1993-1994 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Literary: Essay: SSA History, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Literary: General, 1975-1979, undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Literary: General: Society of American Archivists, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Literary: Institutional Directory (1 of 4), 1993 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Literary: Institutional Directory (2 of 4), 1993 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Literary: Institutional Directory (3 of 4), 1993 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Literary: Institutional Directory (4 of 4), 1993 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Literary: Institutional Directory, undated (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Literary: Institutional Directory: Notes, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Literary: Leadership List, 1990-2006 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Literary: Leadership List, 1990-2013 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Literary: List of Leaders, 2007 January (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Literary: Lists of Officers, 2003-2005 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Literary: List of Past Presidents and Annual Meeting Sites (1972-2017), 2015 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Literary: Mailing Lists, 1980-1981, undated (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Literary: Mailing List, circa 2010 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Literary: Membership Lists, 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Literary: Membership Lists, 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Literary: Membership Lists, 1975-1978 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Literary: Membership Directory, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Literary: Membership Directory, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Literary: Membership Directory, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Literary: Membership Directory, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Literary: Membership Directory, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Literary: Membership Directory, 1989-1990 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Literary: Membership Directory, 1990-1991 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Literary: Membership Directory, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Literary: Membership Guide, 1996 May (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Literary: Membership Directory, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Literary: Membership Directory, 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Literary: Membership Directory, 2000-2001 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Literary: Membership Directory (1 of 2), 2002-2003 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Literary: Membership Directory (2 of 2), 2002-2003 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Literary: Membership Directory, 2004-2006 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Literary: Membership Directory, 2006-2008 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Literary: Membership Directory, 2008-2010 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Literary: Minutes: Membership Business Meeting, 2013-2016 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Literary: Notes: General, 1988, undated (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Literary: Notes: Mark Lambert, 2000-2012, undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Literary: Notes: Society of American Archivists, undated (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Literary: Organizational Meeting (1 of 2), circa 1972 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Literary: Organizational Meeting (2 of 2), circa 1972 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Literary: Political Bill #2758, circa 1989 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Literary: Press Releases: Creation of SSA, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Literary: Registration Materials: Creation of SSA, 1972, undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Literary: Report: "Planning for the Archival Profession: A Report of the SAA Task Force on Goals and Priorities", 1984 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Literary: Report: Society of American Archivists, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Literary: Report: Texas A&M University Archives, 1985-1986 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Literary: Resumes, undated (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Literary: Rosters of Officers and Committee Members, 2002-2004 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Literary: SAA Writing Guidelines, 2007 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 1978-1979 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 1980-1983 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 1984-1985 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 1985-1989 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 1993 Fall/1994 Winter (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 1994 Summer (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 1994 Fall (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 1994 Winter/1995 Spring (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 1995 August (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 1995 November (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, circa 1996 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 1998 February (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 1998 May (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 1998 August (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 1998 November (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 1999 February (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 1999 May (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 1999 August (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 1999 November (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2000 February (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2000 May (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2000 August (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2000 November (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2001 February (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2001 May (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2001 August (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2001 November (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2002 February (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2002 May (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2002 August (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2002 November (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2003 February (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2003 May (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2003 August (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2005 May (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2005 August (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2005 November (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2006 February (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2006 May (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2011 May (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2011 August (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2011 November (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2012 February (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2012 November (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2013 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, 2015 February (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Literary: SSA Newsletter, undated (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Literary: Tours: Society of American Archivsts, undated (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Literary: Website, undated (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Literary: Workshop Opinionnaires, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Photograph: Malcolm McLean, circa 1988 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Audio Cassette: Untitled, undated (Box 46 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - Digital Media: Directory and Mailing List, circa 2010 (Box 46 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - Digital Media: "Louisiana Archives and Manuscripts Association", undated (Box 46 OVZ, Folder 16)
  - Digital Media: Photographs: Carol Bartels, undated (Box 46 OVZ, Folder 17)
  - Digital Media: SSA Databases: Q&A 3.0, undated (Box 46 OVZ, Folder 18)
  - Digital Media: SSA Website, 2009 September 23 (Box 46 OVZ, Folder 19)
  - Artifact: Badge: 40th Anniversary, 2012 (Box 48 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Artifact: Gavel, undated (Box 48 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Artifact: Pencils (3), undated (Box 48 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Artifact: Pin: "Archives", undated (Box 48 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Artifact: SSA Water Bottle (1 of 2), undated (Box 48 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Artifact: SSA Water Bottle (2 of 2), undated (Box 48 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Artifact: Stamp: "Official SSA Ballot", undated (Box 48 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - Literary: Certificate of Merit: Nancy L. Boothe, 1996 May 18 (Box [1063] OVZ, Folder 11)